Taylor Foster

Certified Project Management Professional

600-00-0001 • alex.murphy@gmail.com • San Francisco, CA

Summary

Result-orientated project team leader with 5 years of experience covering project and product management including developing, implementing and supporting complex infrastructures for fast growing startups. A fast and eager learner, I am deta oriented and adapt to changing project requirements quickly to meet business goals.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

San Francisco, CA **Rover Games** 2019 - Ongoing Senior IT Project Manager

Rover Games is a multi-play mobile game app development firm that has successful titles such as Drink Something, Trivia Tonight and King's Fight

- Accelerated outbound sales cycle by 330% by designing and implementing customer acquisition platform for training and managing technical and IT teams
- Established and curated strategic partnerships with 6 out of 10 top state manufacturing companies which resulted in \$20M additional annual revenue
- Led re-architect effort of a core SaaS product to reduce the platform deployment time for clients by 2 months

Los Angeles, CA Tesla 2017 - 2019 Project Manager

Tesla is an electric vehicle manufacturer that is revolutionizing the automobile industry

- Lead a team of developers to build a proprietary CRM system for enterprise and its strategic partners, optimizing sales process and increasing sales revenue by 24%
- Curated a \$2M business implementation project that saves ~ \$3.5M on operational inefficiencies between sales and development departments

Los Angeles, CA Reilly Group 2016 - 2017

Customer Success, Product Support

Reilly Group is a full service technology solutions provider

- Researched user behavior and led strategic product roadmap discussion across multi functional teams
- Integrated Tableau reporting system into BI sales workflow, which led to 23% increase in post-meeting inquiries for technical sales department
- Streamlined post-sales support to increase customer retention rate among enterprise clients by 27%

Los Angeles, CA Wolf Industries 2015 - 2016 **Project Coordinator**

Wolf Industries is a home appliance part supplier to major appliance manufacturers including GE

- Acted as liaison between 3 country offices
- Maintained and documented inventory of over 4,000 items
- Led a team of 15 as a project manager, creating a trusting, respectful team in the process
- Consistently ranked in the department's top 3 for completed tasks
- Trained over 270 temporary remote workers

Education

University of California, Berkeley Bachelor of Science, Industrial Engineering Berkeley, CA 2011 - 2015

Powered by CY Enhancy